The road to prom can be a big hairy mess.
Bad Hair Day is a comedy, adventure, tv movie film directed by Érik Canuel.
Monica is desperate to be prom queen, but on the big
night, her hair is an uncontrollable mess.
Meanwhile, FBI agent Liz Morgan is on the hunt for a jewel thief who is
looking for a stolen necklace, which Monica has in her possession.
Soon, she and the agent chase the jewel thief, and she's
whizzed on a wild adventure in the city.
Monica Reeves, played by Laura Marano.
Liz Morgan, played by Leigh-Allyn Baker.
Pierce Peters, played by Christian Campbell.
Sierra, played by Kiana Madeira.
Ed, played by Christian Paul.
Père de Monica, played by Alain Goulem.
Bad Hair Day is a 2015 crime comedy film released as a Disney Channel Original Movie which
premiered on February 13, 2015, starring Laura Marano and Leigh-Allyn Baker.
The story centers on 16-year-old Monica Reeves, who is
running for Prom Queen at her high school.
One day, she wakes up with crazy hair after
combining loads of different products.
But Monica soon has bigger things to worry about when ex-police Lieutenant Elizabeth "Liz"
Morgan arrives at Monica’s door in search of a $7 million diamond necklace.
The two become unlikely friends as they race to fix Monica’s hair for prom and protect the
necklace from falling into the hands of a world-renowned jewel thief, Pierce Peters.
The film explores themes of detective, prom, school,
high school student, crime gone awry.
The tone is lighthearted.